softbuy.com 2011-06-05

# 

This privacy policy covers the privacy practices for the Softbuy website (collectively, the "website" located at www.softbuy.com). Softbuy, a branch of Brothersoft, the provider of the website (referred to as "us" or "we"), is committed to protecting your privacy online. 

We reserve the right to modify the privacy policy at any times. So please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of notice on our home page. 

Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the “User” or the “End User”) and how we use that information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us. By visiting the Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

Softbuy regards the privacy of users seriously. Email and other personally identifiable information of users are valued on the website.

We will not share, sell, rent, or trade your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties unless:  
1\. Users affirmatively agree to such disclosure.  
2\. Users opt in to receive information and service from a third party.  
3\. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.  
4\. to protect and defend rights or property of other users of our Webite

 **Personally Identifiable Information**

We may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Partners, Affiliates and Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information (which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information) with “Third Party Advertisers” or “Third Party Advertising Companies” and other parties as provided below:

We use Third Party Advertising Companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Some of these Third Party Advertising Companies may be advertising networks. 

We also cooperate with software publishers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or share the information with software publishers for registration code generation purpose. Please note that this is not Personally Identifiable Information, only general summaries of the activities of our Users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by Softbuy.

Security Instructions

You can access your Personally Identifiable Information on our Website through a password and your email address. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. We also advise you to close your browser window when you quit using Softbuy or the services provided by Brothersoft, if you access the Website from a public Internet cafe, for example.
